export const questions = [
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 3+4?',
      options: [8, 4, 7, 9],
      correctAnswer: 7,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 6+2?',
      options: [8, 9, 7, 5],
      correctAnswer: 8,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 5+5?',
      options: [11, 9, 10, 8],
      correctAnswer: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 2+1?',
      options: [8, 6, 4, 3],
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 2+2?',
      options: [3, 4, 6, 8],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 6+6?',
      options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
      correctAnswer: 12,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 7+2?',
      options: [9, 10, 6, 11],
      correctAnswer: 9,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 6+4?',
      options: [12, 11, 10, 9],
      correctAnswer: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 7+7?',
      options: [10, 11, 12, 14],
      correctAnswer: 14,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 8+8?',
      options: [12, 15, 16, 14],
      correctAnswer: 16,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 3-2?',
      options: [3, 1, 2, 0],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 5-1?',
      options: [4, 3, 2, 1],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 4-2?',
      options: [4, 1, 2, 3],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 6-3?',
      options: [5, 2, 3, 1],
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 4-3?',
      options: [5, 2, 7, 1],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 7-2?',
      options: [6, 5, 4, 2],
      correctAnswer: 5,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 8-4?',
      options: [6, 5, 4, 7],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 9-1?',
      options: [2, 8, 10, 5],
      correctAnswer: 8,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 10-3?',
      options: [1, 3, 5, 7],
      correctAnswer: 7,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 7-6?',
      options: [3, 1, 5, 7],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 2x3?',
      options: [11, 4, 6, 9],
      correctAnswer: 6,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 1x2?',
      options: [4, 2, 3, 6],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 4x3?',
      options: [3, 6, 9, 12],
      correctAnswer: 12,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 5x2?',
      options: [10, 11, 12, 5],
      correctAnswer: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 3x3?',
      options: [3, 9, 4, 7],
      correctAnswer: 9,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 5x4?',
      options: [15, 20, 10, 5],
      correctAnswer: 20,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 7x3?',
      options: [12, 14, 16, 21],
      correctAnswer: 21,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 2x8?',
      options: [9, 14, 16, 12],
      correctAnswer: 16,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 9x2?',
      options: [18, 15, 19, 12],
      correctAnswer: 18,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 10x1?',
      options: [1, 10, 0, 11],
      correctAnswer: 10,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 4/2?',
      options: [2, 4, 6, 8],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 5/1?',
      options: [3, 2, 1, 5],
      correctAnswer: 5,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 4/4?',
      options: [0, 3, 2, 1],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 6/2?',
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4],
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 7/7?',
      options: [1, 2, 5, 7],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 6/1?',
      options: [2, 6, 3, 7],
      correctAnswer: 6,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 8/4?',
      options: [7, 6, 4, 2],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 9/3?',
      options: [1, 2, 3, 6],
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 10/2?',
      options: [2, 5, 6, 8],
      correctAnswer: 5,
    },
    {
      question: '¿Cuánto es 10/5?',
      options: [2, 5, 1, 4],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
  ];